[ 480p | 720p | Movies Download | Mkvking.com ]
It feels so spooky here at night.
I feel rather uncomfortable.
Whose idea is it
to hold the test of courage here?
What if ghosts appear?
Isn't it too late to say that?
"Just don't turn your head on the stairs."
The rumor is meant to scare the juniors.
-And you believe it?
-It seems real!
-How did the girl die?
-She was killed.
-Bullshit.
-Hush! It's starting.
Attention please, juniors.
This year, the test of courage
is held at the forbidden spot
in Tung Hu University,
the Female Ghost Bridge.
You guys will be starting from here.
When you hear the bell,
take off the red cloth
and circle around the lake.
Go.
Please do remember.
No matter what happens,
never turn your head on the stairs.
One, two.
What is he doing?
-Why is he counting the steps?
-Three.
-Didn't we agree not to count?
-Four, five.
-Let him count.
-Six.
-It's more exciting.
-Seven, eight.
-No, we can't do that.
-Nine.
-Wen-yao, stop counting!
-Wen-yao!
-Ten, eleven, twelve.
Thirteen.
-Wen-yao!
-Fourteen.
Where has he gone to?
Wait.
Did we just turn around on the steps?
-No.
-Did we?
What was that?
FEBRUARY 28, 2020
Test the sound.
One, two, three, four.
RECORD OF SUPERNATURAL STORIES ON CAMPUSES
Numerous ghost stories
have been circulating
among students in many colleges.
Like the haunted elevator
at Chinese Culture University.
The Moon Lake at Taiwan University.
The Lixing campus
at Cheng Kung University.
Meanwhile, Tung Hu University
that was founded 62 years ago
is a hotbed for ghost stories.
The best-known forbidden spot
is the Female Ghost Bridge.
It was built for the convenience
of the students.
It didn't have a name back then.
Later, rumor has it
that a girl was dumped by her boyfriend.
She had waited for him till midnight.
In the end, she couldn't take it
and drowned herself in the lake.
Since then,
an extra step would suddenly appear
on the stairs
at midnight.
Today is February 28, 2020.
It's a very special year.
A leap year.
Four years ago, today,
a clip of a test of courage
was posted online.
A white shadow appeared in the end.
Let's find out if it is the legendary...
ghost.
The most terrifying thing is that
all five students in the clip had died.
Their bodies were found
scattered around campus.
It should have been a case
that shocked the entire country,
but no one followed it up.
RISKING LIVES FOR TEST OF COURAGE
Was it due to the pressure
from the university
that the police covered it up?
Or did the ghost
drive them to commit suicide?
Let me find out about the truth.
They say that at midnight,
an extra step will appear
on the original 13-step stairs
on the Female Ghost Bridge.
At that moment, never turn your head
because the ghost might be
right behind you.
Today is February 28,
the date the incident happened.
Let's check how many steps there are
during the day.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten,
eleven, twelve, thirteen--
I'm sorry. One more take.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You were a news anchor.
Why did they send you to do this?
Don't pick on my wound.
No one watches the morning news anyway.
At least, these are real.
Things that really happened.
So, you think the story is true?
The ghost killed people?
There is always some truth in a story.
Never believe what you see on the surface.
I'll definitely dig something up.
Don't worry. I'll get my old job back.
The price you pay for surviving
is so high.
Here.
Ready?
Wait.
Let's start when you're ready.
Five, four, three, two...
Let's see how Sung and Yu-ching
get on with the props.
Hey, can't you borrow a normal classroom?
Well, I only have keys
to the classrooms in my department--
So many eyes are staring at you!
You feel comfortable?
Actually, I enjoy the attention
I get like this.
Okay, let's see the result
of our hard work!
Come!
Goodness.
Could that be a supernatural phenomenon?
Supernatural your ass!
It means you have to do it again!
I'm off to film the others.
You guys keep flirting with each other.
You haven't interviewed me yet!
No one wants to interview you!
Or you can interview her!
-Come interview me.
-No!
-So annoying!
-Stop messing around!
I forgot to start streaming.
TUNG HU NATIONAL UNIVERSITY, LIVE START
Hello, juniors.
I'm Hsin-chiao,
a postgraduate in the student union.
The test of courage
will take place tomorrow.
Let's check what the captain
and the duty officer are doing.
Let's go!
Shall we change a place?
It's too dangerous to do it
on the Female Ghost Bridge.
Why didn't you say it earlier?
Well, we can still change it.
Of course not.
You know very few people
have signed up for this event.
But so many joined the test of courage
held at Chinese Culture University.
They did it before us.
We must get more people!
Are you stupid or something?
Safety comes first!
You didn't bring it up back then.
Everything is ready.
Are all law students as stupid as you?
Me?
Te-chuan, look at her!
So mean!
This is the captain, Meng Po-ju.
We call her "San-nu."
What is this?
Chi Te-chuan.
You're so out of the loop!
I'm doing livestreaming.
So what should I say?
Don't be harsh on him.
Then say something on his behalf.
I'll do it.
This is Te-chuan, a third-year student
in Mass Communication.
He's the duty officer this year.
His favorite pastime
is scaring girls!
That's why the test of courage
is being held
on the Female Ghost Bridge.
I didn't choose the place.
It has nothing to do with me.
So who chose the goddamn place?
Well, it's you.
No, I remember it was--
No need to discuss something like this.
Let's go check if everything is ready
for tonight. Let's go!
Well, I'm really curious
about who chose the place.
-You're so annoying.
-It's really haunted.
-So scary!
-It's not scary.
You're the scary one. The scariest.
I'm scary?
You had better...
Wait.
What?
Please stop filming.
TUNG HU NATIONAL UNIVERSITY, LIVE END
Do you have to be like this?
Can't we talk nicely to each other?
I've said everything I needed to say.
Just look after yourself.
You still won't come back to me?
I'm giving you one more chance.
Would you stop making a scene?
What are you guys doing?
Nothing. It's all set.
-Te-chuan, it's dark here!
-Okay.
Go to hell then.
We agreed not to show my face.
Stop filming.
Don't make me lose my job
for so little money.
I'm sorry.
We have stopped filming.
You guys are so bothersome.
Are you sure I won't be seen?
I promise.
You can talk now.
A group of students met with an accident.
They committed suicide
in very strange places.
All in different places?
That's what they told the public.
The creepiest thing is
they all drowned.
The bridge and the dorm
were cordoned off years ago.
But those bloody kids
just wouldn't listen.
What do you think?
Scary, right? Come here.
Put this on and hide behind the tree.
When you hear my cue, you dart out.
Why don't you put it on
and wait for my cue?
Because you look scarier!
What the hell? Do I look scary?
You're the scary one.
Even ghosts will be scared!
I wasn't that mean, was I?
I didn't mean it.
Don't be angry.
If I become a ghost,
you're the first on my list!
Why don't I turn you into one now?
Don't hit so hard! Are you serious?
Are you guys ready?
-I'm going to film the others.
-Okay.
We just need to adjust it a bit.
Come on, hurry up!
What are you doing?
-Have you started streaming?
-Not yet.
I'm testing the light.
So I'll leave the filming
to you two mass communication students!
I'll shoot behind-the-scenes footage
with this camera.
Come on, sit down.
I can't start shooting until you sit.
I don't want to sit here!
Goodness, just sit down.
We're all here. No need to be scared.
I'll protect you if anything happens.
It's almost midnight.
I'm about to start streaming.
You guys at the back! Ready?
-Yes, ready!
I'm the one left here.
You just don't care about how I feel!
Aren't you an IT student?
Why are you afraid of ghosts?
You know, according to quantum mechanics,
ghosts do exist!
We study liberal arts.
I don't understand a word you're saying.
-What?
-Hold it.
Damn! Why do you blindfold me?
Are you playing tricks on me
or the juniors?
We have to do it for real.
You remember the rundown?
No, I don't!
We'll start streaming on the bridge!
The bell tied to the chair is your cue.
You just take off the blindfold
and walk up the bridge.
Remember, don't count the steps!
When we are done, go back to Room 414!
Why is it taking so long?
Are we starting yet?
Stop messing around.
Attention please, juniors.
This year, the test of courage
is held at the forbidden spot
in Tung Hu University,
the Female Ghost Bridge.
You guys will be starting from here.
When you hear the bell,
take off the red cloth
and circle around the lake.
Go.
Please do remember.
No matter what happens,
never turn your head on the stairs.
One, two, three, four...
-What is he doing?
-Six.
Did someone ask him to count the steps?
Didn't we agree not to count?
Let him count.
It's more exciting.
No, we can't do that. Wen-yao!
Wen-yao, stop counting! Wen-yao!
-Wen-yao!
-Eleven.
-Wen-yao, stop counting!
-Fourteen.
-Wen-yao!
There really are 14 steps.
Who did that?
Aren't we all right here?
Where has he gone to?
Where is Wen-yao?
You guys are so damn childish!
Wait.
Did we just turn around on the steps?
-It doesn't count, does it?
-No.
Did you do that too?
It wasn't me.
Let's go!
You tried to trick me?
I'll scare you bastards to death!
TE-CHUAN: THE CHAIR WAS A GOOD TRICK
REMEMBER TO PACK UP THE CAMERA
What chair?
That doesn't count
as turning my head, right?
Forget about the camera.
Yes?
Turn the screen to the brightest.
Yes, this is as bright as it gets.
Why is it getting dimmer?
Turn the screen to the brightest!
Turn the screen to the brightest.
This is as bright as it gets.
-What the hell?
-This is as bright as it gets.
Turn the flashlight on.
It's on.
Shit.
I thought there was someone.
I'm here.
What on earth happened just now?
Was that you?
No, it wasn't me!
So why did we start running then?
Someone started running
and the rest just followed suit!
What the hell is going on?
Calm down, okay?
Didn't we say we would go back
to the dorm first?
Let's go back to the dorm first.
Wen-yao didn't reply to my text.
Should we go look for him?
You and Wen-yao played a trick on us.
Didn't you?
I won't admit it without any evidence.
I can smell crime.
So what are you?
A judge or psychic?
Here is the evidence!
In that case,
I've snatched the evidence back!
Silly you!
Put me down or they will see us.
We'll make it public then.
But we're just having a fling.
That really hurts.
I'm doing it for your sake, all right?
I know.
Besides, if she hears about it,
it will be hard for you to deal with it.
Don't you worry about that.
I didn't break up with her properly.
I'm sorry.
I'm happy as long as
we can see each other.
I'm only happy when I'm with you.
All right.
Let's go look for Wen-yao.
He's not replying to my text at all.
So annoying!
Where are the others?
Why did we bother
to hold the test of courage on the bridge?
I'm going to karaoke later.
It's so late!
We have an event tomorrow morning.
I don't understand why we were assigned
to a deserted dorm.
It's so spooky here!
Don't be scared.
I'll be back soon to keep you safe.
Okay.
I'm going to the restroom.
Wait until I get back.
It's all right.
Wen-yao!
Where has he gone?
It has already had more than 10,000 views!
Why are there so many views?
What does this comment mean?
"They even showed the ghost
in the advertisement."
Wait.
-That's it, isn't it?
-Let me see.
HSIN-CHIAO: ARE YOU SEEING SAN-NU?
It's just a smudge on the screen.
Is it Wen-yao?
No.
They're asking if we have found Wen-yao.
He hasn't gone back to the dorm?
DON'T THINK TOO MUCH
No, I don't think so.
WE'LL TALK AFTER THE EVENT
It's so late. Where did he go?
I'm the only friend you have.
Who are you chatting with?
Bullshit.
I've got tons of friends, okay?
Then why did you follow me
to Tung Hu University?
You could have gone to a better one.
Give it back to me!
Just tell me you're talking to Sung.
I'm just wondering
why he has been gone so long.
I was only asking.
Wait.
Something is going on
between you two, right?
No, something's going on at the bridge!
Who is it?
Is it you, Sung?
Go have a look.
It's nothing.
It was the wind.
Hello?
You'll be a bit late?
Okay.
Yu-ching?
So, Yu-ching cares about me.
Pong!
Fifty thousand.
No need to choose.
They all stink.
Fuck!
It's occupied! You hear me?
Fuck! What's wrong with you?
Damn. Let me see who it is.
Fuck!
Let go of me!
Let go of me! Fuck!
Let go!
What the hell?
No.
"Team Tung Hu put in so much effort."
"They went all out."
"You can see the ghost even in the promo."
"There is a white shadow at the back.
Run, quick!"
These were the comments posted
after the livestreaming that day.
We can see that everyone was crazy
about the rumor
of the Female Ghost Bridge.
Okay. Cut!
What's the point of filming this?
We can do an insert.
Team B sent us a clip.
Didn't they go film the Taoist monk?
Master, what has the accident in 2016
got to do with the Female Ghost Bridge?
The ghost needs to find her replacement.
Those who died in the leap year
are forever trapped in hell.
The same tragedy
may happen again this year!
There are people on the bridge.
The bad vibes are the thickest today.
Another five people will die.
Don't go! Leave now!
So, the rumor of the Female Ghost Bridge
is true?
Let me check the livestream again.
Didn't five students die before?
And it will happen again?
I think I saw something.
Rewind it.
Look!
He didn't even pack up the camera.
Where on earth did Wen-yao go?
I have no idea.
We saw no signs of him
like he was a ghost.
Don't say something like that.
What? Don't be so superstitious.
Don't take chances at a time like this.
Don't be skeptical.
So you believe in the rumor of the bridge?
Then why did you hold the event here?
I didn't agree with it.
So whose idea is it?
I think Wen-yao must have gone back.
He would send a text if he did.
Let me call him.
How did this happen?
Should we check the CCTV footage
at the security office?
Okay.
Come in. Don't let others see you.
I'm not sure if the file is still intact.
No records before year 2012 were saved.
Find it yourself.
Be quick.
"Men's Dorm 11."
Year 2012.
Year 2013, 2014, 2015.
Year 2016, here it is.
February.
February 28.
I've got it.
One, two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
These must be the five students
that died in the accident.
It's the footage of them
returning to the dorm.
Check which room they stayed in.
Okay.
Hello?
The papers are here?
I'll send someone to get them.
I need to copy the files. Go pick
something up for me at the front gate.
Right.
Okay.
There is no one here.
I guess they're patrolling the campus.
Should we just check
the monitor ourselves?
That's illegal.
You can keep watch.
Why should I be your accomplice?
We don't know when the guards
will be back.
If anything happens to Wen-yao,
won't we be charged with manslaughter?
Manslaughter?
So persuasive.
That's why you fell for me.
We don't know who fell for whom yet, okay?
Sung didn't answer the call?
It didn't go through.
Miss.
Can you stop pacing back and forth?
Then come to the restroom with me.
Okay.
Let's go.
Look over here.
What are you doing?
Usually, I'm the one who gets scared.
Now it's your turn.
Beg me.
Whatever!
Just hurry up.
Where are you going?
The restroom is over there.
Sung is there.
I want to go to the other side.
Are you sure you don't want to run?
No. It will leak if I run fast.
This is as fast as I can go.
Stop laughing!
I can't hold it if I laugh!
Yu-ching, come on!
See? You wanted to pee too, right?
You're not filming, are you?
Yu-ching.
Yu-ching?
Why did you come from the outside?
Were you not in the restroom too?
No, I wasn't.
Are you done?
What?
Someone is in there.
What are you doing?
Let me check.
Otherwise, no one
will be able to sleep tonight.
-No, don't.
-It's fine.
I scared you, didn't I?
Don't be such a pain in the neck!
Go to your beloved Sung!
Chao Hsin-chiao, wait for me!
Why did it get so dirty?
Hsin-chiao!
Hsin-chiao, wait for me!
Ghosts that haunt colleges.
There are lots of ghost stories
of the Daren Building
at Chinese Culture University, right?
The building was built in the shape
of an upside-down Bagua.
It's a perfect place for ghosts.
The haunted elevator
is the best-known story.
Haunted elevator?
Yes, a teacher went to check.
He pressed the first floor,
but the elevator didn't stop.
It kept going down and never came back up.
That story about
Chinese Culture University is so scary.
The story of the Female Ghost Bridge
is scarier.
What exactly happened on the bridge?
Didn't she drown herself in the lake?
Not at all.
It's not true.
So what really happened?
One year,
a female student decided to elope
with her boyfriend.
They agreed to meet on the bridge.
The girl kept waiting till midnight,
but there was no sight of her boyfriend.
At that moment,
someone appeared on the steps
and waved at her.
Just as she stepped on the 13th step,
she was dragged into the woods
and raped by five men.
No matter how she struggled
and begged them,
they refused to let her go.
In the end,
she was pushed into the lake and drowned.
Ever since then,
every day at midnight,
an extra step would appear
on the 13-step bridge.
At that moment,
-never turn your head around.
-Twelve, thirteen.
If you do,
the ghost
-will be right in front of you.
-Fourteen.
You're so mean!
Why are you being so serious?
If you dump me like the guy in the story,
I won't wait for you on the bridge.
Don't wait for me.
You had better go reincarnate.
You're finished!
I'll strangle you to death!
Okay, I surrender!
Seems like someone else is here.
There's nothing.
Yes, right...
That's weird.
Didn't you see it?
The head is moving.
What head?
There is something.
What?
I saw something.
But there shouldn't be anyone
at this time.
It must be Wen-yao.
Let's go to the makeup classroom.
Let's go.
Come on.
Why is it taking so long to wash it off?
Was I being too much?
Hsin-chiao!
Wait for me!
What the hell?
Help...
Sung?
Is that you?
What are you doing?
What happened to you?
The doors are closing.
What on earth is Wen-yao doing?
I wonder what the others are up to.
Te-chuan.
This is B1.
Didn't we press the fourth floor?
What's going on?
The doors are closing.
Why isn't it going up?
San-nu.
What's wrong?
There really was something in there.
There's nothing.
Why don't you believe me?
I do. It's...
Don't be scared.
I'll protect you if anything happens.
Can we go back?
We'll go back as soon as
we find Wen-yao, okay?
-Let's go.
-Okay.
This is Room 414.
When the incident happened,
five students had spent the night here.
At--
What's wrong?
I'm not feeling well.
It smells in there.
Damn you, Yu-ching.
Did you have to be so annoying?
You're still hiding?
What are you doing?
Who's there?
Hsin-chiao!
No, not that way!
Strange.
Why did Wen-yao go back to the classroom?
Wen-yao.
Don't go in there.
Wait for me here.
Let me turn on the lights.
I'll go check.
It's not working.
Let me check the back for another switch.
Be quick!
Wen-yao.
Wen-yao!
Te-chuan...
Wen-yao.
San-nu.
Wen-yao! Where are you going?
Te-chuan, where are you?
Te-chuan.
Come out now, Te-chuan.
Stop messing around!
Te-chuan, you're over there, right?
Te-chuan!
Stop messing around!
It's not funny!
Te-chuan!
San-nu!
Go!
Call someone!
There is no signal.
Quick!
Wait.
Why did you stop?
Don't you find it strange?
We've been going down so many floors.
I don't care! I just want to get out!
Yu-ching!
Get up.
How did we end up here?
We're doomed.
Yes, we're doomed!
Don't worry.
We'll find a way down.
Shih Yu-ching!
Pull yourself together!
I'll protect you.
We shouldn't have played the game.
We won't be able to get away.
We can't escape.
I don't want to die.
-There must be a way.
-I don't want to die.
I don't want to die.
Yu-ching, get up!
We can get--
STUDENT UNION OFFICE
What are we doing here?
It's the office of those students
who had died.
See what you can find.
I'll check the files.
It has been four years.
What clues do you expect to find?
Check every nook and cranny.
Okay.
TUNG HU NATIONAL UNIVERSITY
How did you get the statement
from the police?
It's better if you don't know.
Te, come film this.
"Li Wen-yao.
He was found drowned
underneath the bridge.
Meng Po-ju.
Also drowned in some corners
of the campus.
Cheng Lin-en, Li Tien-ming."
Both of them drowned too.
Only Chao Hsin-chiao
went missing.
Why did they all drown
in such strange places?
-What?
-Look.
There were six people.
Let me replay it.
But only five students
were mentioned in the statement.
Right here.
There were six people that day.
Only five were mentioned
in the police file.
Only five were reported in the news too.
How about the sixth student?
Don't get any closer.
Follow me!
Hsin-chiao? Come.
It's okay.
What just happened?
Wait.
Why are we walking towards the bridge?
San-nu, let's go!
San-nu!
Yu-ching.
Yu-ching!
Why am I back here?
Is that you?
What are you doing here?
Didn't you say you'd protect me?
Yes.
I said I'd protect you.
Didn't you say
you'd protect me?
Yu-ching.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
Where is she?
I thought you were leaving?
Why did you come back?
I thought we should take a look at these.
Photos of the student union
from the past few years.
And?
We could check and find out
who the sixth student was.
That's odd.
"Meng Po-ju."
"Li Wen-yao."
"Li Tien-ming, Cheng Lin-en."
"Chao Hsin-chiao."
Only Chao Hsin-chiao
is in the group photo.
Why aren't the others such as
Meng Po-ju or Li Wen-yao in here?
Who are these five people
we've never seen?
This photo was taken in 2012.
TUNG HU THE BRAVEST!
But what we are investigating
happened in 2016.
I must have missed something.
You mean something happened
in 2012 as well?
Didn't the test of courage on
the Female Ghost Bridge go wrong in 2016?
So it was stopped after that.
I remember a strange article on BBS.
Maybe you should look it up.
FEMALE GHOST BRIDGE, TUNG HU UNIVERSITY
"Five people died on the bridge.
A news blackout was imposed.
It wasn't reported."
But there wasn't a news blackout.
This was posted in 2012.
On the same date in 2012,
a test of courage was held
on the bridge too.
You guys keep flirting with each other.
You haven't interviewed me!
No one wants to interview you!
Or you can interview her.
-Come interview me.
-No!
-So annoying!
-Stop messing around!
Hello?
Where are you?
I forgot to start streaming.
FEBRUARY 28, 2016
Hello, juniors.
I'm Hsin-chiao,
a postgraduate in the student union.
The test of courage
will take place tomorrow.
Let's check what the captain
and the duty officer are doing.
Let's go!
I'm going to film the others.
Okay. We just need to adjust it a bit.
Hurry up! You're so slow.
FEBRUARY 28, 2012
What are you doing?
Nothing.
We are ready. Come on.
Hurry up!
It's almost midnight.
You guys hurry up!
Okay.
-Have you started streaming?
-Not yet.
I'm testing the light.
FEBRUARY 28, 2016
You guys at the back! Ready?
-Yes, ready!
I'm the one left here.
You just don't care about how I feel!
Aren't you an IT student?
Why are you afraid of ghosts?
What happened to the students in 2012?
Hsin-chiao!
Shih Yu-ching!
Pull yourself together!
I'll protect you.
I'm sorry.
Chao Hsin-chiao survived.
Four years later,
she took part in the event again.
Another four people died.
What sort of person was she?
What on earth did she experience
that brought her back again?
There must be some connection.
Please, I beg you to spare me.
I'll do anything.
You still won't come back to me?
I'm giving you one more chance.
Would you stop making a scene?
What are you doing?
Nothing. Is everything ready?
Go to hell then!
Remember.
No matter what happens,
never turn your head around.
One, two.
What is he doing?
Didn't we agree not to count?
Let him count.
It's more exciting.
Didn't we just turn our heads?
Chao Hsin-chiao!
Why did you choose her over me?
What happened to us
had nothing to do with her!
You're behind all these tricks,
aren't you?
All of you deserve to die!
I gave you a chance.
I thought you would protect me.
I do want to protect you.
But we really aren't meant for each other!
Please, I beg you to let me go!
Let San-nu go, please. I beg you!
Don't hurt San-nu!
Te-chuan.
Help!
San-nu...
I'm sorry.
Te-chuan.
Help!
I'm the one left here.
You just don't care about how I feel!
If you dump me like the guy in the story,
-I won't wait for you on the bridge.
-All of you deserve to die!
Help!
I'll protect you.
Don't be scared.
I'll protect you if anything happens.
I'll strangle you to death!
-Why don't you believe me?
-Ghosts do exist.
-All of you deserve to die!
-Stop it!
You said you'd protect me!
I'm sorry.
Don't kill me.
I don't want to die.
Are you really afraid of dying?
You killed Wen-yao
and the others, didn't you?
You have to die too.
Don't kill me.
I'll do anything you ask me to do.
Do you think I never tried?
She won't let me go.
I shouldn't have broken the spell
on the bridge.
I can't die even if I want to.
But I want to live on!
Stop talking!
It's no better
to live on.
For four years,
every time I close my eyes,
I saw those five faces.
Are you sure you want to live on?
It's a high price to pay.
There must be a way.
There must be a way, right?
Hit my head with it.
Today,
five people must die.
Kill me.
Kill me!
It's easy to keep yourself alive.
Will you kill to keep yourself alive?
Come on.
Come on!
Kill me and you'll live!
They are Meng Po-ju, Chao Hsin-chiao,
and Li Wen-yao.
Where is the group photo taken in 2016?
Did you find anything?
There is nothing here.
Maybe earlier?
How much earlier?
When did the rumor of the bridge start?
More than 30 years ago, I guess.
Hello?
SEARCH: CAMPUS DEATHS, BRIDGE
The people for the reenactment shoot
are here.
I'll get ready on the bridge.
Do you really have to shoot
the scene at midnight?
You wanted it real, right?
It happened exactly four years ago today.
UNKNOWN DEATH ON CAMPUS,
FEMALE STUDENT FOUND UNDER BRIDGE
DEATH ON CAMPUS,
REPUBLIC OF CHINA CALENDAR,
YEAR 69, FEBRUARY 29
It's February 29 again.
So, something is bound to happen
on February 29 every four years?
11,50 P.M.
Oh, no. Te is on the bridge.
It's hard to live on.
I've suffered a lot to survive.
If I want to live,
five people must die today.
I heard that people had died
on this bridge.
It has to be fake news.
But the seniors say
it's true that the bridge is haunted.
Seriously? You really believe it?
I don't care as long as we are paid.
-Everyone.
-Yes?
I need you to walk up the stairs
and count the steps.
Then, turn around.
Okay?
-Yes.
Ready.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
-One, two, three, four, five,
-six, seven,
-eight, nine, ten,
-eleven, twelve, thirteen,
-fourteen.
I need your help
to break this cycle.
-Five.
-Four.
-Three.
-Two.
-One.
It's your turn.